unbiasedwriter.com 2019-06-24

# PRIVACY POLICY - Unbiased Writer

This Privacy Policy applies only to UnbiasedWriter.com (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise), or other interactive features that are accessible or downloadable through UnbiasedWriter.com and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Web Site”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Web Site, and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Company (unless specifically stated).

_**NOTICE REGARDING ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING**_

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**_NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES AND YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY_**  
By using the Web Site, you acknowledge your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Company may update this Privacy Policy. However, Company will use your personal information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy.
